<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">How to, League of Legends</string>
    <string name="mapas_alternativos">Alternative maps</string>
    <string name="o_que_e">What is League of Legends?</string>
    <string name="monstros_mapa_principal">What are the monsters?</string>
    <string name="o_mapa">How work the main map?</string>
    <string name="quem_criou">Who created League of Legends?</string>
    <string name="texto_o_que_e">League of Legends is a fast-paced, competitive online game that blends the speed and intensity of an RTS with RPG elements. Two teams of powerful champions, each with a unique design and playstyle, battle head-to-head across multiple battlefields and game modes. With an ever-expanding roster of champions, frequent updates and a thriving tournament scene, League of Legends offers endless replayability for players of every skill level.</string>
    <string name="a_maior_comunidade">World\'s Largest Online Gaming Community</string>
    <string name="a_maior_comunidade_expli">Join the world\'s largest online gaming community: make friends, form teams and battle tens of millions of opponents from countries across the globe, then exchange strats on reddit, YouTube, the forums and beyond</string>
    <string name="competicao_do_seu_jeito">Compete Your Way</string>
    <string name="competicao_do_seu_jeito_expli">Whether you\'re enjoying a game against bots or climbing the ranks of the league system, League of Legends has the tech to quickly match you with a group of similarly-skilled competitors</string>
    <string name="crie_estrategias_e_evolua">Strategize and Evolve</string>
    <string name="crie_estrategias_e_evolua_expli">With regular gameplay updates, multiple maps and game modes, and new champions constantly joining the League, the only limit to your success is your own ingenuity </string>
    <string name="entre_no_mundo_dos_esports">Experience eSports</string>
    <string name="entre_no_mundo_dos_esports_expli">As the world\'s most active competitive scene, League of Legends sports numerous tournaments worldwide, including the prestigious Championship Series where salaried pros compete for millions</string>
    <string name="lute_com_honra">Fight with honor</string>
    <string name="lute_com_honra_expli">Compete with honor and receive special commendations from your peers to reward your good sportsmanship</string>
    <string name="lute_mano_a_mano">Battle Head-to-Head</string>
    <string name="lute_mano_a_mano_expli">Combine strategic thinking, lightning reflexes and coordinated team-play to crush your enemies in both small-scale skirmishes and intense 5v5 battles</string>
    <string name="riot_games">We aspire to be the most player-focused game company in the world. We were established in 2006 by a couple of entrepreneurial gamers who believe player-focused game development can result in awesome games. In 2009, we released our debut title, League of Legends, to critical and player acclaim. Over 67 million play every month.  We know players form the foundation of our community and it’s for them that we continue to evolve and improve the League of Legends experience.</string>
    <string name="a_experiencia_primeiro_lugar">PLAYER EXPERIENCE FIRST</string>
    <string name="a_experiencia_primeiro_lugar_expli">We obsess over every part of the experience, from a player’s first game to their thousandth win, from installation to support to esports broadcasts. It all matters.  We listen to what players say and do. We analyze. Then we make data-informed decisions to improve the experience. </string>
    <string name="quebre_paradigmas">CHALLENGE CONVENTION</string>
    <string name="quebre_paradigmas_expli">Impossible’s our favorite kind of possible.  Doing the right thing often requires disregarding the rules and upending the status quo.</string>
    <string name="foco_no_talento">FOCUS ON TALENT AND TEAM</string>
    <string name="foco_no_talento_expli">We attract, develop, and cultivate entrepreneurial teams who prefer action over process and bureaucracy.  We’re a sports team, not a family.  As a meritocracy, we value results delivered.</string>
    <string name="levamos_jogo_a_serio">TAKE PLAY SERIOUSLY</string>
    <string name="levamos_jogo_a_serio_expli">It’s never just a game.  We play lots of games and proudly call ourselves gamers. Even at work, we make time for daily play and fun.  We’re professionals, but don’t take ourselves too seriously. </string>
    <string name="continue_faminto">STAY HUNGRY, STAY HUMBLE</string>
    <string name="continue_faminto_expli">We strive to be humbitious – ambitious and humble.  Complacency kills innovation, but ambition kills complacency.  We humbly seek and accept feedback.  We credit the larger team: the families, teammates and players who make it all possible.  And we believe there’s always more we can do for players.</string>
    <string name="defender_e_destruir">Defend and Destroy</string>
    <string name="defender_e_destruir_expli">The gold standard for competitive League of Legends. Action on Summoner\'s Rift often progresses in unique phases, beginning with small-scale duels between lane opponents before culminating in epic, large-scale team fights. Push your way into the opposing base, destroy the enemy nexus, and achieve victory!</string>
    <string name="a_batalha_pela_fenda">The Battle for the Rift</string>
    <string name="a_batalha_pela_fenda_expli">The largest map in League of Legends, Summoner\'s Rift is mirrored diagonally and features three lanes into the enemy base. Each lane is defended by three turrets and an inhibitor, while the nexus is protected by a pair of turrets. Both sides of the map boast expansive jungles containing powerful buffs, and the central river is home to two boss monsters and a scuttle crab that provide team-wide benefits.</string>
    <string name="terreno_neutro">Neutral Ground</string>
    <string name="a_selva">The Jungle</string>
    <string name="a_selva_expli">The mirrored jungle areas on Summoner\'s Rift each contain several lesser monster camps that grant unique powers when the summoner spell \'Smite\' is used on them, along with a pair of more powerful monsters that buff the slaying champion for a longer duration. Managing your jungle buffs is essential to maximizing performance on the battlefield, so be wary of any enemy you spot entering your jungle. If you\'re not careful, you may find he\'s stolen your buffs!</string>
    <string name="o_dragao">The Dragon</string>
    <string name="o_dragao_expli">Located in the river near bottom lane, this neutral monster is usually best handled as a group. Defeating the dragon grants a permanent stacking "Dragon Slayer" buff, with a massive bonus granted at 5 dragons slain. The dragon also gains bonus damage and takes less damage from opponents who have higher stacks of the Dragon Slayer buff.</string>
    <string name="barao_nashor">Baron Nashor</string>
    <string name="barao_nashor_expli">This dangerous monster makes his lair in the river near top lane. A hard fight, even for five well-equipped champions, Baron Nashor is the most challenging neutral encounter in League of Legends. Defeating this massive wyrm grants the massively powerful \'Hand of Baron\' buff to all living champions.</string>
</resources>